Guide to the Terri Hendrix Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2018-033
  - CDs - Live recordings and interviews, 1997-2015
    - Arhaven House Concerts, TX (3 discs), January 4, 2015 (Box 2751)
    - Crossroads w/Lloyd Maines (2 copies), April 18, 2015 (Box 2751)
    - Wings Point w/Lloyd Maines (2 copies), November 7, 2015 (Box 2751)
  - CDs - Live recording and interviews, undated
    - Uncle Calvin's Coffeehouse, 30th Anniversary (Box 2751)
    - Music & Entertainment, Kara Grainger/Terri Hendrix (3 copies) (Box 2751)
    - Music & Entertainment Live: Terri Hendrix (Box 2751)
    - Live at Lucy's Boathouse (2 discs) (Box 2751)
    - Live at KUT/Waterloo (Box 2751)
    - KSIL Radio Interview (Box 2751)
    - Live at KGSR "One Way" (Box 2751)
    - Texas Music Cafe, "Class of 87" Episode #702 (Box 2751)
    - KUT Live from Studio 1-A w/Lloyd Maines (Box 2751)
    - Live at the Armadillo Bazaar (2 discs) (Box 2751)
    - Evening Star Radio Show w/Lloyd Maines (2 copies) (Box 2751)
    - Red River Radio, Shreveport, LA (part 2) w/Lloyd Maines (Box 2751)
    - Live at the World Café, Volume 11 "Places in Between" (Box 2751)
    - Arhaven House Concerts (4 discs) (Box 2752)
    - Evening Star Radio Show (Box 2752)
    - ME Television: Eliza Gilkyson (Box 2752)
    - Live at Cibolo Creek (Box 2752)
    - "Goodtime Van" live at KGSR Radio, Austin, TX (Box 2752)
    - Humble Time! #91 Texas Songwriter's Radio Showcase La Kiva, Terlingua (Box 2752)
    - Terri & Lloyd KPIG (Box 2752)
    - Kerrville Folk Festival (Box 2752)
    - "Goodtime Van" recorded at KGSR (Box 2752)
    - Live at Gruene Hall (Box 2752)
    - KBEC (Box 2752)
    - Europe "D" label (Box 2752)
    - Live at Gene Shay Folk Show. "H" label (Box 2752)
    - Live at WLUW 88.7 FM w/ Lloyd Maines. "K" label (Box 2752)
  - CDs - Various Recordings
    - Life's a Song 1 (3 copies) (Box 2752)
    - Life's a Song 2 (8 copies) (Box 2752)
    - Life's a Song 1st weekend, 2007 (Box 2752)
    - Life's a Song 2nd weekend, 2007 (Box 2752)
    - Susan Session #1 (Box 2752)
    - Session #2 (Box 2752)
    - Ray and Terry [sic] (Box 2752)
    - Terri Hendrix (hand drawn lettering on cover) (Box 2752)
    - Terri Hendrix (Box 2752)
    - Programs and other stuff (Box 2752)
    - Texas Matters and Songs (4 discs) (Box 2752)
    - Funky Mix 2, December 2006 (Box 2752)
    - Hole/Still 2/4 (Box 2752)
    - Preachers, June 18, 2017 (Box 2752)
    - Slaughterhouse (Box 2752)
    - Betty Elders, Light in Your Window (2 copies) (Box 2752)
    - Cowboy (Box 2753)
    - KSIL Pictures (Box 2753)
    - Richard's Terri Mix (Box 2753)
    - Terri's Song (Box 2753)
    - KGSR "one way" (Box 2753)
    - Funky Blue Goat Mix 2 (Box 2753)
    - Adam's Mix (Box 2753)
    - imix for Terri (Box 2753)
    - Goat Mix vol 4 (Box 2753)
    - Terri Hendrix (Box 2753)
    - Terri Town 3 (Box 2753)
    - Remembering Jeannie (Box 2753)
    - Old Enough (Box 2753)
    - Glenn Songs (Box 2753)
    - Glenn Sampler no 2 pt 1 (Box 2753)
    - Glenn 01-05 (2 copies), January, 2005 (Box 2753)
    - 1 funky itunes tine (Box 2753)
    - Biggers' mixes, January 10, 2011 (Box 2753)
    - Gravity (Box 2753)
    - Waltz Loop (Box 2753)
    - Here I am / Book Kells / Near (Box 2753)
    - Territown A (Box 2753)
    - Terri Hendrix RWRS vols 1-3 (3 discs) (Box 2753)
    - Burn (Box 2753)
    - Paul's Tunes, October 17, 2001 (Box 2753)
    - Glenn 101 (Box 2753)
  - CDs - Potentially Production
    - Love You Strong (17 cds) (Box 2753)
    - Commercial 1-5x "with Blue Eyed", November 20, 2006 (Box 2753)
    - One Way (Box 2753)
    - Two Dollar Shoes, Tsunami Sound & Video (Box 2753)
    - Terri Work CD, Kerrville (Box 2753)
    - Live in San Marcos studio cuts, August 2, 2001 (Box 2753)
    - Places in Between Master (Box 2753)
    - Live Recordings Master, 1st Ref, February 16, 2001 (Box 2753)
    - Newest Terri Live Reference (Box 2753)
    - Between (Box 2753)
    - The Ring "Master? Remix?" (Box 2753)
    - The Ring. Premixes (Box 2753)
    - The Ring. 1st Version Roughs (Box 2753)
    - Mixes, January 20, 2000 (Box 2754)
    - Mixes, undated (Box 2754)
    - Terri Hendrix Live, unmastered (Box 2754)
    - April 2, 2002 (Box 2754)
    - The Ring. Premix (Box 2754)
    - P.F.F., 2006 (Box 2754)
    - Demo Reel (Box 2754)
    - Two Dollar Shoes, October 12, 1997 (Box 2754)
    - Lloyd's CD ideas for "Acre of Land", February 2007 (Box 2754)
    - Ideas (4 discs) (Box 2754)
    - Master, June 5, 2007 (Box 2754)
    - Clicker (Box 2754)
    - Drum Loops, June 14, 2013 (Box 2754)
    - w/ Mi Madre (Box 2754)
    - Children's Record, Sequenced, October 5, 2005 (Box 2754)
    - Children's Record, 1st Ref Master, October 16, 2005 (Box 2754)
    - Children's Record, 2nd Master, October 17, 2005 (Box 2754)
    - Love You Strong, Masters (5 discs) (Box 2754)
    - Terri Hendrix '04, Master, April 13, 2004 (Box 2754)
    - The Ring. Rough (Box 2754)
    - Master for Duplication, April 19, 2004 (Box 2754)
    - Final Master for Duplication, April 17, 2004 (Box 2754)
    - Master Ref, (2 discs), December 11, 2015 (Box 2754)
    - Demo #1, 2006 (Box 2754)
    - Retrospective, Work CD (Box 2754)
    - Rockin, Ruff (Box 2754)
    - Terri Hendrix (with note from Bruce Chandler), 2008 (Box 2754)
    - Terri '04 AORW ruffs, 2004 (Box 2754)
    - Ruffs, March 4, 2010 (Box 2754)
    - Spiritual Kind, Master Ref, March 4, 2012 (Box 2754)
    - Spiritual Kind, Master Ref, March 5, 2012 (Box 2754)
    - Wilory 8I (Box 2754)
    - Wilory Farm 8II (Box 2754)
    - Wilory Farm (Box 2754)
    - TH Wilory Test (Box 2754)
    - Cowboy in Texas, March 10, 2005 (Box 2754)
    - Cowboy Ruff, February 10, 2005 (Box 2754)
    - 10 unidentified CDs/DVDs (Box 2754)
    - 11 unidentified CDs/DVDs (Box 2755)
  - CDs - Produced
    - The Art of Removing Wallpaper (3 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Celebrate the Difference (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Christmas at Wilory Farm (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Friendswood & Beyond (3 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Left Over Alls (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Live (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Live in San Marcos (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Love You Strong (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Places in Between: Project 5.1 (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - The Ring (Box 2755)
    - Slaughterhouse Sessions: Project 5.2 (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Spiritual Kind (3 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Terri Hendrix (3 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Two Dollar Shoes (2 copies) (Box 2755)
    - Wilory Farm (4 copies) (Box 2755)
  - CDs - Compilations
    - Kerrville Folk Festival 2000, vol 1 (Box 2756)
    - Travelin Texas (Box 2756)
    - New Music, vol 6 (Box 2756)
    - Highway Prayer: A Tribute to Adam Carroll (Box 2756)
    - Interlude, 1997-2007 (Box 2756)
    - Voices from a Grateful Nation, vols 1 & 2 (Box 2756)
    - Playlist 2.0 (2 copies) (Box 2756)
    - Big Sweet Life: The Songs of Jon Dee Graham (Box 2756)
    - Believe Children Can (Box 2756)
    - Rip it. Burn it. Live it (Box 2756)
    - Dreamer: A Tribute to Kent Finlay (Box 2756)
    - A Song to Old San Marcos (2 copies) (Box 2756)
    - Moments of Grate: A.R.T.S. for People (Box 2756)
    - SXSW, vol 5 (Box 2756)
    - Lone Star Sampler, vol 1 (Box 2756)
    - Performing Songwriter (Box 2756)
    - Songwriter's Toolbox (4 copies) (Box 2756)
    - Live at the World Café, vol 11 (Box 2756)
    - Live at the World Cade, vol 9 (2 copies) (Box 2756)
    - Midnight Special: live from the Folk Alliance conference, Austin TX (Box 2756)
  - DAT Tapes
    - Terri Hendrix (Box 2756)
    - Two Dollar Shoes-Master (Box 2756)
    - Terri/Lloyd Tin Angel, June 8, 2000 (Box 2756)
    - [illegible] Safety copy, June 18, 1997 (Box 2756)
    - Terri H. Vox, October 1997 (Box 2756)
    - Terri Hendrix: Master – Safety (Fire Station Studio), September 25, 1997 (Box 2756)
    - Terri Hendrix – Master (Box 2756)
    - Two Dollar Shoes (Box 2756)
    - Unlabeled (Fire Station Studio) (Box 2756)
  - VHS Cassettes
    - "Gruenefest '93" (Box 2757)
    - "Musician Audition: Terri Hendrix. KVUE 24, Austin, TX", March 1998 (Box 2757)
    - "Reality w/ Terri Hendrix and Jaston Williams of Greater Tuna", June 7, 1998 (Box 2757)
    - "Terri Hendrix Cibolo Creek CC, KLRN Ch-9 TV", July 29, 1998 (Box 2757)
    - "The All You Can Eat Texas Music Café: Terri Hendrix", November 5, 1998 (Box 2757)
    - "Terri Hendrix. KEYE", February 12, 1999 (Box 2757)
    - "Texas Summer Nights", March 14, 1999 (Box 2757)
    - "Terri Hendrix. Fox News at 6pm", March 18, 1999 (Box 2757)
    - "Terri Hendrix and Lloyd Maines", April 24, 1999 (Box 2757)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at Uncle Calvin's Coffeehouse", 1999 (Box 2757)
    - "Alain Party", March 14, 2003 (Box 2757)
    - "Lloyd Maines and Terri Hendrix", April 19, 2007 (Box 2757)
    - "Terri Hendrix", undated (Box 2757)
    - "Terri Hendrix and Jim Volk Live at Gruene Hall #2", undated (Box 2757)
    - "Terri Hendrix and Jim Volk Live at Gruene Hall #3", undated (Box 2757)
    - "Terri and Jim Volk", undated (Box 2757)
    - "When I was 20", undated (Box 2757)
    - 6 unlabeled VHS cassettes (Box 2757)
    - Hedwig and the Angry Men (Box 2757)
    - Blues3 Harmonica (Box 2757)
    - 10 VHS cassettes, "1A," "1B," "2A," "2B," "3A," "3B," "4A," "4B," "5A," "5B" Possibly Live from Cibolo Creek Country Club (Box 2757)
  - DVDs
    - Terri Hendrix and Lloyd Maines live at Casbeers, January 13, 2006 (Box 2758)
    - Outstanding Young Alumni Awards Banquet, Hardin Simmons University, February 11, 2001 (Box 2758)
  - U-Matic Tapes
    - Live from Cibolo Creek Country Club, KLRN (Box 2759)
  - Digital Audio Minidiscs
    - "Cool Riff 1-2" (Box 2759)
    - "#1 Pretty Piece, #3 Lifes Song Upbeat" (Box 2759)
    - "Wahet Harp, Goat Harp, New 06" (Box 2759)
    - "#1 Anita #2 Pretty #3 Wine Bottles", February 20, 2007 (Box 2759)
    - "2004 Licks Etc" (Box 2759)
    - "Do You Hear, Heard Bells, Wind Up" (Box 2759)
    - "Ideas" (Box 2759)
    - "Difference #7" (Box 2759)
    - "Pastures Plenty" (Box 2759)
    - "Stay", January 7, 2004 (Box 2759)
    - "Stay", December 2003 (Box 2759)
    - "Culture Vulture, Instrumental, Stay," "With band first time", January 8, 2004 (Box 2759)
    - "Jacob Thron, Your Ladder" (Box 2759)
    - "Trains New" (Box 2759)
    - "Djembe Madness" (Box 2759)
    - "Irish Stay", December 2003 (Box 2759)
    - "2004 New" (Box 2759)
    - "One Way Waltz" (Box 2759)
    - "Dec 2003 New Stuff" (Box 2759)
    - "Wine Bottles" (Box 2759)
    - "New Cool Riffs 2005" (Box 2759)
  - Computer Files
    - External Hard Drive (Box 2759)
    - "Janson Text font for Shiner," 3.5" floppy disk (Box 2759)
    - June 2010 thumb drive (Box 2759)
    - Memory Card, 2GB (Box 2759)
  - Posters
    - Encore for Advocacy, Kessler Theatre, Jimmy LaFave, Slaid Cleaves, Eliza Gilykson, Terri Hendrix, April 5, 2012 (Box 2760)
    - Cibolo Creek Country Club, 10th Anniversary, 1990-2000 (Box 2760)
    - Longview Museum of Art, Sara Hickman and Terri Hendrix, December 3, 2011 (Box 2760)
    - Uncle Calvin's Coffeehouse, Terri Hendrix with Lloyd Maines, Brooks Williams, and Hans Theessink, November 16, 2007 (Box 2760)
    - Orpheum Theatre (Phoenix), David Bromberg with Angel Band and Terri Hendrix, June 10, 2007 (Box 2760)
    - Hillside Gardens, Terri Hendrix. October 16, no year (Box 2760)
    - Spiritual Kind Promo poster (Box 2760)
  - Other Oversized
    - Smithsonian Folklife Festival Award, 2008 (Box 2760)
    - Proofs for Spiritual Kind CD cover (Box 2760)
    - 2 pieces of artwork (Box 2760)
    - Framed collage (Box 2760)
  - Political buttons and ephemera (mostly anti-George W. Bush) (Box 2761)
  - Artist badges and back stage passes (Box 2761)
  - Painted overalls worn for performances (Box 2762)